http://www.impactanalytical.com/privacy.aspx

Call
Contact
Privacy
Privacy PolicyImpact Analytical respects the privacy of and is committed to protecting the personal information it obtains from its website's readers. Generally, the reader can browse through the Impact Analytical website without providing any information. However, sometimes personal information is required to provide requested services or the reader may choose to provide Impact Analytical with personal information for better service.
Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Impact Analytical will not intentionally transfer personal information to third parties without the reader's consent. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
The Impact Analytical website and My Impact service uses cookie technology for the sole purpose of session identification only. The cookie resides on the user's computer, and stores no personal information. Impact Analytical safeguards the security of the data sent to us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. The Impact Analytical website and the My Impact service strive to protect the personal information of its users by employing SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) technology, which encrypts information as it travels between a user's computer and Impact Analytical servers. Impact Analytical's website contains links to other sites. Impact Analytical does not share its readers' personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices.
Your Access to and Control Over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website.
SecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
SurveysFrom time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or other emails. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
Have a Question?
Give Us a Call:
Copyright © Impact Analytical.
All Rights Reserved.
